You're never as alone as you think.
The Shack is a drama, family film directed by Stuart Hazeldine.
A grieving man receives a mysterious, personal invitation to
meet with God at a place called 'The Shack'.
Mack Phillips, played by Sam Worthington.
Papa / Elouisa, played by Octavia Spencer.
Willie, played by Tim McGraw.
Jesus, played by Aviv Alush.
Sarayu, played by Sumire.
Nan Phillips, played by Radha Mitchell.
The Shack is a 2017 American fantasy drama film, directed by Stuart Hazeldine and written by
John Fusco, Andrew Lanham and Destin Daniel Cretton, based on the 2007 novel.
The film stars Sam Worthington, Octavia Spencer, Avraham Aviv
Alush, Radha Mitchell, Alice Braga and Tim McGraw.
The story follows a grieving father who, after suffering a family tragedy, receives a mysterious invitation to visit a shack
deep in the wilderness, where he confronts his darkest fears and experiences a transformative spiritual journey.
Filming began on June 8, 2015, in Vancouver, British Columbia.
The Shack was released in the United States on March 3, 2017.
The film received unfavorable reviews from critics, but grossed
$96.9 million against a budget of $20 million.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, loss of
loved one, christianity, guilt, death of daughter.
The tone is uplifting and emotional.